Guide to the Stanford University, Program in Human Biology, Lectures [videorecording]
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videos
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1988/89. Ken Prewitt. Private Foundations in Global Environment, Jun 5 1989; V246.343; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. [unknown]. [untitled], Apr 1 1988; V246.344; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. [unknown]. [untitled], Apr 4 1988; V246.345; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. [unknown]. [untitled], Apr 6 1988[?]; V246.346; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Roland Ciaranello, Shirley Feldman. [untitled], Apr 11 1988; V246.347; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Roland Ciaranello, Sanford Dornbusch. [untitled], Apr 13 1988; V246.348; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Dennis Baylor, Arthur Wolf. [untitled], Apr 15 1988; V246.349; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. [unknown]. [untitled], Apr 18 1988; V246.350; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. [unknown]. [untitled], Apr 22 1988; V246.351; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, Archibald. [untitled], Apr 29 1988; V246.352; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, Archibald. [untitled], May 2 1988; V246.353; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. James Lawry, Archibald. [untitled], May 4 1988; V246.354; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. James Lawry, Archibald. [untitled], May 6 1988; V246.355; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. James Lawry, David Maron. [untitled], May 9 1988; V246.356; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, David Maron. [untitled], May 11 1988; V246.357; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, Lipset. [untitled], May 13 1988; V246.358; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, Lipset. [untitled], May 16 1988; V246.359; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. James Lawry, Rice. [untitled], May 18 1988; V246.360; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. James Lawry, Fagan. [untitled], May 20 1988; V246.361; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, Crapo. [untitled], May 23 1988; V246.362; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, Herant Katchadourian. [untitled], May 25 1988; V246.363; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B. Spring 1987/88. Craig Heller, Herant Katchadourian, May 27 1988; V246.364; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology Fall 1988/89. Ina Roy. Population Genetics., Nov 17 1988; V246.365; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology Fall 1988/89. Ina Roy. Population Biology., Nov 21 1988; V246.366; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 131. Peter Duignan. Some consequences of diseases in Africa, Apr 5 1988; V246.367; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 131. Great Neglected Diseases. Dr. Barry R. Bloom. Leprosy, May 3 1988; V246.368; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - Human Biology 131. Great Neglected Diseases. Richard A. Young. Stress response to disease, May 5 1988; V246.369; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 27)
  - lecture #3 [possibly continuation of H.B. 3A Winter 1987/88. Frank Stockdale. Cells and Tissues], 1/11/88; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 27)